<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The Deshiknaves Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://deshiknaves.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://deshiknaves.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-09-16T23:15:07+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://deshiknaves.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Deshiknaves]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Octopressin' it.]]></title>
    <link href="http://deshiknaves.github.com/blog/2012/09/16/finally-octopressin-it/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-16T19:54:00+10:00</updated>
    <id>http://deshiknaves.github.com/blog/2012/09/16/finally-octopressin-it</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>And so it starts</strong></p>

<p>Been meaning to get a blog up so that I could write down some of the things I learn about on a daily basis building applications. I figure that this is one way to document some of the techniques that I figure out - and then then do forget about if it&#8217;s not a common occourance. This way I can quickly write a little bit about it and have it there for later reference. And it might help out someone who has has the same issue. Eitherway, it&#8217;s mainly about my journey as a devleoper.</p>

<p>I could spend a bunch of time designing and building a blog, but that&#8217;s just not needed, it&#8217;s about the content. With the fact that there is going to be a lot of code references, <a href="http://octopress.com">Octopress</a> seems to be perfect for my own needs. Not having an admin interface and just bein able to write a blog post from the command line and markdown is just perfect for what I need. I haven&#8217;t quite checked out all the internal workings of this application yet, but it does seem weird not to have a database to store the data. But this is an awesomely put together blogging framework.</p>

<p>Now to figure out some of the finer details of this blog.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
